const QUIZ = [
  {
    question: "Batman is the alter-ego for which billionaire playboy?",
    options: ["Bruce Wayne", "Dick Grayson", "Thomas Wayne", "Michael Keaton"],
    answer: "Bruce Wayne"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the official creator of Batman?",
    options: ["Tim Burton", "Bob Kane", "Christopher Nolan", "Zach Snyder"],
    answer: "Bob Kane"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Though it is not conclusively proven, in the comic books, who murdered Thomas and Martha Wayne?",
    options: ["Alfred Pennyworth", "Jack Napier", "Joe Chill", "Joker"],
    answer: "Joe Chill"
  },
  {
    question:
      'In "Batman: The Animated Series" who plays the voice of the Joker?',
    options: ["Tim Curry", "Jared Leto", "Jack Nicholson", "Mark Hamill"],
    answer: "Mark Hamill"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the original Robin?",
    options: ["Dick Grayson", "Jason Todd", "Damien Wayne", "Tim Drake"],
    answer: "Dick Grayson"
  },
  {
    question: 'Which villain is known for referring to Batman as "Detective"?',
    options: ["Joker", "Penguin", "Two Face", "Ra's Al Ghul"],
    answer: "Ra's Al Ghul"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Solve my puzzles to find out my name. I use to be known as Edward Nigma. Some call me a genius everyone; else calls me insane. My trademark is the question mark, and my puzzles will leave you stumped. Who am I?",
    options: ["Riddler", "Joker", "Two Face", "Clue Master"],
    answer: "Riddler"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Only one of Batman's sidekicks has held both the mantle of Batgirl AND Robin. Who is this character?",
    options: [
      "Helena Wayne",
      "Cassandra Cain",
      "Stephanie Brown",
      "Barbara Gordon"
    ],
    answer: "Stephanie Brown"
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am the head of Wayne Enterprises Research and Development Labs, and Batman would not exist without me because I made his weapons. If he needs an upgrade, I'm the first person he calls. Who am I?",
    options: ["Alfred Pennyworth", "James Gordon", "Lucius Fox", "Jack Ryder"],
    answer: "Lucius Fox"
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am the man who broke Batman! I was born and raised in prison, but I escaped and rely on an addictive drug for my superb strength! Who am I?",
    options: ["Arcady", "Bane", "Frenzy", "Kick"],
    answer: "Bane"
  }
];
